Isabella Karle and Jerome Karle Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Oversize, 1958-2000 (Box OV 1-OV 65)
  - Isabella Karle Papers
    - Research File
      - Frog 219A, crystallographic data printouts, 1985 (Box OV 37)
      - White, Steven, chapter, figures and illustrations, circa 1990-circa 1993 (Container 115, same heading) (Box OV 3)
      - Mg Pentapeptide
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1983 (Container 117, same heading) (Box OV 37)
        - Figures and illustrations, circa 1970-circa 1984 (Container 117, same heading) (Box OV 4)
      - Leu-zervamicin, figures and illustrations, circa 1990 (Container 118, same heading) (Box OV 65)
      - Vernamycin, crystallographic data printouts, 1981 (Container 122, same heading) (Box OV 37)
      - Lysozyme research
        - Crystallographic data, circa 1958 (Box OV 38)
        - Diffractograms, circa 1956-circa 1957 (Box OV 39-OV 41)
        - Diffractograms, circa 1957-circa 1958 (Container 122, same heading) (Box OV 3, OV 42-OV 43)
      - HEX PEP SS, crystallographic data printouts, 1986 (Container 126, same heading) (Box OV 38, OV 44)
      - ILKKCPBL, Gábor B. Fodor, crystallographic data printouts, 1987 (Container 127, same heading) (Box OV 44)
      - Bodanszky, Miklos, crystallographic data printouts, 1987 (Container 127, same heading) (Box OV 44)
      - Phe GAGP, crystallographic data printouts, 1981 (Container 132, same heading) (Box OV 45)
      - Antaminide analog
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1980 (Container 136, same heading) (Box OV 46)
        - Figures and illustrations, circa 1971-circa 1982 (Container 136, same heading) (Box OV 65)
      - Huisgen, Rolf, crystallographic data printouts, 1979-1984 (Container 137, same heading) (Box OV 46)
      - "OV1"
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1973, 1981 (Container 138, same heading) (Box OV 45)
        - Figures and illustrations, undated (Container 138, same heading) (Box OV 45)
      - HEXAI, crystallographic data printouts, 1983 (Container 138, same heading) (Box OV 44)
      - Mg(Hexpep)₂ and restrained refinement, figures and illustrations, circa 1978-circa 1981 (Container 139, same heading) (Box OV 65)
      - MGHP x-ray diffractometer results, 1979-1980 (Box OV 47-OV 48)
      - C-pentapeptide, crystallographic data printouts, 1976-1977 (Container 140, same heading) (Box OV 49)
      - C-APG dPhe P, crystallographic data printouts, 1981-1984 (Container 140, same heading) (Box OV 49)
      - VALINO/DMSO
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1974 (Container 140, same heading) (Box OV 50)
        - Figures and illustrations, undated (Container 140, same heading) (Box OV 50)
        - Figures and illustrations, 1987 (Container 140, same heading) (Box OV 65)
      - Valino PI
        - Miscellany, figures and illustrations, circa 1969-circa 1974 (Container 140, same heading) (Box OV 65)
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1974-1975 (Box OV 50-OV 52)
      - U10
        - Figures and illustrations, circa 1981-circa 1987 (Container 140, same heading) (Box OV 65)
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1987 (Container 141, same heading) (Box OV 52)
      - ENKEPH
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1980-1983 (Container 141, same heading) (Box OV 52-OV 53)
        - Figures and illustrations, 1982 (Container 141, same heading) (Box OV 53, OV 65)
      - DECAISO, crystallographic data printouts, 1987 (Container 142, same heading) (Box OV 54)
      - MONO DECA ZA 1-10, figures and illustrations, circa 1986-circa 1989 (Container 142, same heading) (Box OV 65)
      - INDIADECA
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1985 (Container 142, same heading) (Box OV 54)
        - Figures and illustrations, 1985 (Container 142, same heading) (Box OV 65)
      - INDHEXDEC
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1985-1987 (Container 146, same heading) (Box OV 55)
        - Figures and illustrations, circa 1985-circa 1987 (Container 146, same heading) (Box OV 65)
      - Li perhydro antam
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1974-1976, 1985-1986 (Container 147, same heading) (Box OV 56)
        - Figures and illustrations, circa 1974-circa 1988 (Container 147, same heading) (Box OV 65)
        - Figures and illustrations, 1986 (Container 147, same heading) (Box OV 56)
      - Cycloamanide A, crystallographic data printouts, 1980-1983 (Container 147, same heading) (Box OV 55)
      - Cycloamanide polymorphs, crystallographic data printouts, 1980-1981 (Container 147, same heading) (Box OV 54)
      - ASC backup tapes, crystallographic data printouts, 1984 (Container 149, same heading) (Box OV 57)
      - LLLL and LDLL tetrapeptide (Karen), crystallographic data printouts, 1980 (Container 149, same heading) (Box OV 57)
      - Sym Antam
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1985 (Container 149, same heading) (Box OV 58)
        - Figure, undated (Container 149, same heading) (Box OV 3)
        - Figures and illustrations, circa 1974-circa 1986 (Container 149, same heading) (Box OV 65)
      - Levo pimaric, crystallographic data printouts, 1971 (Container 151, same heading) (Box OV 58)
      - "OV2," "OV4"
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1972-1974 (Container 154, same heading) (Box OV 59)
        - Figures and illustrations, 1977 (Container 154, same heading) (Box OV 59)
      - Diffractograms, miscellany, circa 1970-circa 2000 (Box OV 63)
      - Figures and illustrations, miscellany, circa 1970-circa 2000 (Container 163, same heading) (Box OV 63-OV 65)
      - Frog venom research, figures and illustrations, circa 1967 (Container 163, same heading) (Box OV 63)
      - Witkop, Bernhard and J. D. Corbin
        - Crystallographic data printouts, 1968-1973 (Box OV 60-OV 61)
        - Frog venom crystallographic data printouts and illustrations, 1967 (Box OV 61-OV 62)
  - Jerome Karle Papers
    - Speeches and Writings, speeches, glass plates, undated (Container 222, same heading) (Box OV 2)
    - Subject File
      - Electron diffraction, slides, glass plates, undated (Container 368, same heading) (Box OV 2)
      - Figures and illustrations, glass plates, undated (Container 370, same heading) (Box OV 2)
      - Note card file, undated (Box OV 1)
      - Quantum crystallography, miscellany, flow chart, 1991 (Container 390, same heading) (Box OV 4)
      - Slides, miscellaneous, glass plates, undated (Container 405, same heading) (Box OV 2)
      - Vacuum half-box electrometer, blueprints, 1959 (Container 411, same heading) (Box OV 3)
  - Collaborations, Summer School in Modern Methods of Crystal Structure Development, Manchester, England, teaching materials, 1960, Aug. 29-Sept. 9 (Container 423, same heading) (Box OV 3)